We might consider Schrödinger's cat.
Schrödinger. Is that the woman in 2A?
(Sheldon:)No, that's Mrs. Grossinger.
(Sheldon:)She doesn't have a cat, she has a Mexican
hairless. Annoying little animal. Yip-yip-yip.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, you diverted me.
Anyway, in 1935, Erwin Schrödinger,
in an attempt to explain...
(Sheldon:)...the Copenhagen interpretation of quantum
physics, he proposed an experiment.
(Sheldon:)A cat is placed in a box
with a sealed vial of poison...
(Sheldon:)...that will break open at a random time.
Now, since no one knows
when or if the poison has been released...
(Sheldon:)...until the box is opened, the cat
can be thought of as both alive and dead.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, I don't get the point.
(Sheldon:)Well, of course you don't get it.
I haven't made it yet.
You have to be psychic,
there's no such thing...
(Penny:)Sheldon, what's the point?
Just like Schrödinger's cat,
your potential relationship with Leonard...
(Howard:)...right now
can be thought of as both good and bad.